dollarshower.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy - DollarShower.com

**www.dollarshower.com** (henceforth referred to as ‘the site’, ‘the website’, ‘us’ or ‘we’) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our website. Please read the following to understand how we treat any personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

### Collection and use of Personal Information

You are free to use the content of **www.dollarshower.com** without having to provide any personal information whatsoever. For normal web usage, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from our visitors. However, there may be server logging that track low level technical information such as IP addresses, visited URLs, duration of visit or other technical information about visitors. These logs are cleared from time to time.

Any information that is collected while you contact us via the [contact form](http://www.dollarshower.com/contact/) of the site will not be shared with third-parties nor do we store such information on any permanent storage. We hate spam as much as you do. The comments that you create on this blog on any topic of interest requires you to provide your email address and name. This is done with the intent of arresting spam and such collected information is never used for any other purpose.

The site does not store any browser cookies on your system. However, any browser cookies that may be set by the third party services such as Google analytics or plugin software etc, can be turned off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to the website and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include – Google Adsense, Clickbank, [Shareasale](http://www.dollarshower.com/hotdeal/shareasale) and various individual affiliate products.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on the send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

The website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

### Affiliation to third-parties

The site does promote certain products (via ad banners, affiliate links, product reviews etc) that we feel are of good quality and usefulness. However, you are advised to use your judgement before procuring or purchasing such services or products. The site is not responsible for any damage or loss caused to you by these products. Basically, we do not sell any products ourselves but we do promote them. You are requested to contact individual producers of such products in case you encounter any issue.

### Malware-free site

This website is completely free from any kind of malware, spyware or virus that may infect your PC or operations. We are committed to provide you 100% clean technology and quality content that is accessible 24×7. We do not use any malicious third party services that might harm you in any way.

### Plagiarism

The site team is not responsible for any third party misusing or republishing our unique content elsewhere without due permission from us. At the same time, we are committed not to reproduce information from other websites as it is here as well. If at all we do so, the credits are mentioned wherever it belongs. If you notice anybody misusing our information, we request you to kindly notify us of the same.

The images and media used on this website are either produced by us or sourced via proper paid royalty-free channels.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

If you have any further question, please feel free [contact us](http://www.dollarshower.com/contact/).

Site: http://www.dollarshower.com/  
Webmaster: Ajith Prasad Edassery  
Contact: admin@dollarshower.com

This document was last updated on March 15, 2012

Updated by on 1st Jan 2014
